Mss.B.L635
American Philosophical Society
- Papers
  - Houtchens, Lawrence H
  - Howard, Alsa C
  - Howland, Ch C
  - Hroswitha Club
  - Huber, Roger A
  - Huitsinga, J
  - Hull, Charles H
  - Hulme, Edward
  - Hunewell, F W
  - Hungary.
  - Hunt, Emily
  - Huntington, Ellsworth
  - Hutcheson, Austin E
  - Hutchins, Grace
  - Hutchinson, Mrs. Derena M N
  - Hutchinson, W G
  - Hutchinson, William T
  - Huth, C F
  - Icotrump, Minis
  - Imperial Geographical Society of Russia.
  - Independence Hall Association.
  - Independence Hall Project.
  - Independence National Historical Park.
  - Ingersoll, R Sturgis
  - Inman, Samuel Guy
  - Inn, Buck Hill Falls.
  - Institute for Public Service.
  - Institute of Early American History and Culture.
  - Institute of International Education
  - International House, Chicago.
  - International Textbook Company.
  - Italy.
  - Jackson, Joseph
  - James, Reese D
  - Jameson, John Franklin, 1859-1937
  - Jamison, George H, Jr.
  - Japiske, N
  - Jaquette, Mrs. Henrietta Shatton
    Jaquette, Henrietta Stratton, b. 1881
  - Jarman, Peter
  - Jayne, Henry La Barre
  - Jenkins, Charles F
  - Jenkins, Sidney
  - Jenks, Donald
  - Jenks, John Story
  - Jernegan, M W
  - Johnson, Alba B
  - Johnson, Mrs. Alice Adkins
  - Johnson, Allen
  - Johnson, Amandus
  - Johnson, Mrs. Cloyd S
  - Johnson, Douglas W
  - Johnson, Emory R
  - Johnson, R M
  - Johnson, Robert L
  - Jones, Chester Lloyd
  - Jones, Howard M
  - Jones, J D
  - Jones, John R
  - Jones, M Gwladys
  - Jones, P V B
  - Jones, Richard H
  - Jones, Robert Erskine
  - Jones, William Carey
  - Journal of Modern History.
  - Judd, Charles H.
  - Julian, Mrs. A
  - Julius Rosenwald Fund
  - Kamiya, Noburo
  - Kane, Florence Bayard
  - Kane, Margaret L
  - Kapetyn, Paul J
  - Kean, Jefferson Randolph
  - Keedick, Lee
  - Keen, Dora
  - Keen, W W
  - Kempner, Robert M
  - Kennicott, Hiram L
  - Kent, Donald H
  - Keppel, Frederick Paul, 1875-1943
  - Kernel, Robert J
  - Kerr, Chester
  - Keys, Ella Reed
  - Kidder, Alfred Vincent, 1885-1963
  - Killie, Charles A
  - Kimball, Fiske
  - King, C Harold
  - King, Katharine
  - King, Mackenzie
  - Kirshberg, Louis
  - Kirchelder, Otto
  - Kirchner, Walter
  - Klett, Guy S
  - Klingberg, Frank J
  - Klinger, Wallace R
  - Kluckhohn, Clyde K M
  - Knittle, Walter A
  - Knopf, Alfred A
  - Knowlton, Daniel C
  - Kobel, E C
  - Koch, Julie Frotscher
  - Kontz, Louis Knott
  - Koyl, George Simpson
  - Krammer, Samuel N
  - Krebiel, Edward
  - Kroeber, A L
  - Kruse, Mrs. Clarence
  - Ksieniewicz, Casimir A
  - Kurath, Hans
  - Kyte, George C
  - Labaree, Leonard W
  - Laird, Mrs. Clinton N
  - Lampe, M Willard
  - Lancaster, Henry C
  - Lancaster Press Inc.
  - Landeen, W M
  - Lane
  - Langer, William L
  - Latta, Thomas L
  - Lattimore, Owen
  - Laughran, Clayton D
  - Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial
  - Laura Spellman Rockefeller Memorial. Reports
  - Lea, Arthur H
  - Leeb, Harvey
  - Leebrick, R C
  - Lehigh University.
  - Leipziger, Henry M.
  - Leland, Waldo Gifford, 1879-1966
  - Lenape Club
  - Lerando, Leo Zelenka
  - Levis, Frederick
  - Lewis, Edwin O
  - Lewis, John F, Jr.
  - Lewis, Theo J
  - Lewis, W M
  - Lewis Historical Publishing Company.
  - Lichenegger, Augusta
  - Ligget, Robert P
  - Lindsay, Mrs. Alice
  - Lingelbach, Anna
  - Lingelbach, Mrs. Anna
  - Lingelbach, Anna Lane, Home and School Association
  - Lingelbach, Anna Lane, Public School.
  - Lingelbach, Anna Lane, Public School
  - Lingelbach, Egon W
  - Lingelbach, Louise C
  - Lingelbach, Robert L
  - Lingelbach, Suzanne
  - Lingelbach, William Ezra. Autobiography.
  - Lingelbach, William Ezra, Jr.
  - Lingelbach, William Ezra, III
  - Lingelbach, William W
  - Linton, Albert Morris
  - Lippincott, H W
  - Lippincott, Joseph W
  - Lipzer, Fanny
  - Lister, R J
  - Little, Esther L
  - Littleton, Arthur
  - Littleton, William G
  - Lodge, Henry Cabot
  - Logan, John H
  - London School of Economics and Political Science.
  - Lorimer, Graeme
  - Lumbermens Mutual Casualty Company.
  - Lydenberg, Harry M
  - Lynch, Thomas F
  - MacAlister, James
  - McClelland, George W
  - McClung, Clarence E
  - MacColl, Alexander
  - MacCracken, John W
  - McCracken, Robert T
  - McCurdie, Alexander
  - McDaniel, Walter Brooks
  - McDonough, Martha
  - McElroy, R M
  - Macfarlane, John M
  - McFayden, Donald
  - McGill University
  - McGrath, John C
  - McGregor, J C
  - Mack, Caroline S
  - McKay, S S
  - McKeag, Anna J
  - McKee, Kenneth N
  - McKenzie ,R Tait
  - Mackeur, Christian Wilhelm
  - Mackie, Alexander
  - McKinley, Albert E
  - McKinley Publishing Company.
  - McLaughlin, A C
  - McLaughlin, Mrs. Isabel C
  - McLean, S J
  - MacLeish, Archibald
  - McMaster, John B
  - MacMillan, Kerr D
    Macmillan, Kerr D., 1871-1938, Kerr Duncan
  - McMillan, Thomas M
  - Macmillan Company.
  - Maddox, William P
  - Madeira
  - Mahoney, William T
  - Malackey, Sister Mary
  - Maltsberger, J T
  - Manhart, George B
  - Manning, Frederick J
  - Marceau, Henri
  - Margolin, Arnold D
  - Marks, Earl
  - Marriage Council of Philadelphia, Inc.
  - Mayor's Rededication Committee, Philadelphia.
  - Martin, Berthe
  - Martin, Chester
  - Martin, Edward
  - Martin, Lawrence
  - Martin, Sydney E
  - Marts, A C
  - Marvin, Mrs. Mary
  - Marx, Henry F
  - Masaryk, Jan
  - Mason, William Clarke
  - Masters, Harry V
  - Matthews, James J.
  - Matthews, Joseph J
  - Matthews, L Harrison
  - Matveev, Illarion G
  - May, Arthur J
  - Mayor's Rededication Committee, Philadelphia
  - Mead, E S
  - Melvin, Frank E
  - Mentzer, J P
  - Merriam, Charles Edward, 1874-1953
  - Merriam, John Campbell, 1869-1945
  - Merrian, Thornton W
  - Middle States Council for the Social Studies.
  - Middlebush, Frederick A
  - Miller, C William
  - Miller, James C
  - Miller, Karl G
  - Miller, Tina E
  - Mims, Stewart L
  - Miner, H L
  - Mississippi Valley Historical Association.
  - Mitchell, Louise Pearson
  - Mitchell, Lucullus N D
  - Mitchell, Pearl Boring
  - Modern Language Association of America.
  - Moe, Henry Allen
  - Monaghan, Frank
  - Monaton Realty Investing Corporation.
  - Montgomery, James A
  - Moore Institute of Art, Science and Industry.
  - Morgan, Angela
  - Morgan, Marshall S
  - Morgan, William Thomas
  - Morganstierne, Wilhelm
  - Morris, Mrs. Augusta Shippen
  - Morris, Barbara
  - Morris, Edward Shippen
  - Morris, George
  - Morris, Harrison Smith, 1856-1948
  - Morris, John D., and Company.
  - Morris,Richard B
  - Morris, Roland Sletor
    Morris, Roland S., (Roland Sletor), 1874-1945
  - Morris, Samuel W
  - Morrow, Glenn R
  - Moseley, Philip E
  - Moser, Floyd
  - Moses, Jacob M
  - Mowrer Brothers.
  - Mudge, Lewis S
  - Muir, Ramsay
  - Muller, Grover W
  - Mumford, Edward W
  - Mumford, Lewis
  - Munch-Petersen, J H
  - Munro, Dana C
  - Nassau Club
  - Nation.
  - National Board for Historical Service.
  - National Commission on Educational, Scientific and Cultural Cooperation.
  - National Editorial Service.
  - National Encyclopedia of American Biography.
  - National Geographic Society
  - National Missions in the Presbytery of Philadelphia.
  - National Research Council
  - National Resources Planning Board
  - National Society of the Colonial Dames of America in the Commonwealth of Virginia.
  - National Youth Administration Projects.
  - Neely, R Marguerite
  - The Netherlands.
  - Netherlands Study Group.
  - Nettels, Curtis P
  - Neutrality Co-Ordinating Committee.
  - New Commonwealth Institute.
  - New York City. Department of Education.
  - New Helvetic Society.
  - New School for Social Research
  - New York Association for Improving the Condition of the Poor.
  - New York City. Department of Education.
  - New York Public Library
  - New York Times.
  - New Zealand Social Credit Association.
  - Newsweek (magazine).
  - Newton, Joseph Fort
  - Nichols, Grace L
  - Nichols, Isabel
  - Nichols, Mrs. Jeannette P
  - Nichols, Roy Franklin
  - Nitze, William A
  - Nitzsche, George E
  - Nussbaum, Frank F
  - Oakley, Thornton
  - Oberholtzer
  - Oberly, H Sherman
  - Ochs, Adolph S
  - Odell, Glendon T, Jr.
  - Odgers, Merle M
  - Odlozilik, Otakar
  - Office of Price Administration.
  - Ogg, Frederick A
  - O'Hara, Margaret Justin
  - Olmsted, J W
  - Olmsted, Susan H
  - Olp, Ernest E
  - O'Shea, M V
  - Ostroff, Isidor
  - Owen, David
  - Owen, Robert L
  - Oxford University Press
  - Pace, Antonio
  - Paetow, L J
  - Palackar, Stephen J
  - Palmer, Mrs. Helen Walker
  - Pan American Union.
  - Pan-Epirotic Union
  - Panaretoff, S
  - Papers of Benjamin Franklin.
  - Parker, Kate P
  - Passport
  - Patterson, S Howard
  - Paxson, Frederick L
  - Payne, Walter A
  - Pearce, Mary M
  - Pearce, Richard M
  - Peck, Joseph R
  - Penniman, Josiah H
  - Pennsylvania Committee on Penal Affairs.
  - Pennsylvania Committee on the Conservation of Cultural Resources.
  - Pennsylvania Federation of Historical Societies.
  - Pennsylvania Historical Association.
  - Pepper, George Wharton
  - Pepper, Oliver H Perry
  - Perkins, Clarence
  - Peruvian Microfilm, Ltd.
  - Petersen, Howard C
  - Peterson, Charles E
  - Peterson, J Hardin
  - Petrescu, Nicholas
  - Phi Beta Kappa
  - Philadelphia.
  - Philadelphia Alumni Association of Chi Psi.
  - Philadelphia Award.
  - [Philadelphia]. Center City Redevelopment Conferences.
  - Philadelphia Ethical Society.
  - Philadelphia Forum.
  - Philadelphia Geographical Society.
  - Philadelphia Public Schools.
  - Philbrick, Francis S
  - Philips, G M
  - Philomathan Society.
    See Oversized
  - Ph.D.'s in Modern European History...
  - Pinchot, Gifford
  - Pittenger, George W.
  - The Players.
  - PM
  - Poland, Russia.
  - Political Science Quarterly.
  - Pollock, Norman H, Jr.
  - Pomeroy, Mrs. Ada Vere
  - Pomfret, John E
  - Ponapede(?), E
  - Poor Richard Almanac Award.
  - Poor Richard Club.
  - Porter, Charles W
  - Potter, Lloyd G
  - Potts, Katherine B
  - Powell, John H
  - Prason, Paul
  - Presbyterian Church.
  - Presbyterian Ministers Fund.
  - Prilean, A F
  - Princeton University.
  - Proud, Edward
  - Pruit, J W
  - Public Service Electric and Gas Company.
  - Quick, Marette
  - Quinn, Arthur Hobson
  - Quinn, David B
  - Racquet Club
  - Randall, James G.
  - Rankin, H. A.
  - Raven, John H.
  - Read, Conyers
  - Redding, William A.
  - Reid, W Stanford
  - Reither, Joseph
  - Research and Survey Bureau of Philadelphia.
  - Retka
  - Rhoads, Charles J
  - Rhoads, Owen B
  - Rhode Island State College.
  - Richards, Alfred N
  - Richards, Anne
  - Richards, C R
  - Richardson, M M
  - Richardson, Oliver H
  - Ricker, George W
  - Ricker, Gladys B
  - Rigberg, Benjamin
  - Riley, Edward M
  - Rist, Charles
  - Robbins, William Jacob
  - Roberts, Elsie
  - Roberts, Richard Ellis
  - Roberts, W P
  - Robertson, Anne
  - Robertson, David A
  - Robins, Edward
  - Robinson, David M
  - Robinson, Fred N
  - Robinson, Geroid T
  - Robinson, H W
  - Robinson, James Harvey, 1863-1936
  - Robinson, Lawrence M
  - The Rockefeller Foundation
  - Rodman, Walter R
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, pres.U.S., 1858-1919
  - Root, Elihu
  - Root, Winifred T
  - Rorer, J T
  - Rosenbach, A S W
  - Rosenbach, Philip H
  - Rosenbaum, Samuel
  - Rosengarten, J G
  - Rosenwald, Lessing J
  - Rostadtzeff, M
  - Rothermel, Josephine B
  - Rowe, Leo Stanton, 1871-1946
  - Royal Geographical Society.
  - Rubel, Donald C
  - Rugart, Mrs. Helen E Dixon
  - Rule, James N
  - Rumania.
  - Ruml, Beardsley
  - Russian War Relief, Inc.
  - Rustoniger, Ruston
  - Rutgers University
  - Ruthven, Beatrice
  - Rutledge, Anna Wells
  - Schafer, Joseph
  - Saint Augustine, Florida, Project
  - Saint Michaels and Zion Evangelical Luthern Church
  - Salomone, William
  - Samuel, Bernard
  - Sass, Charles
  - Saunders, W. B., Company.
  - Saylor
  - Scandinavia.
  - Scanlon, George F
  - Scattergone, J Henry
  - Schafer, Joseph
  - Schaffner, Gerald
  - Schauss, Adam
  - Schauss, Charles, Estate
  - Schauss, John
  - Schauss(?), Rose
  - Schellenberg, T R
  - Schelling, Felix E
  - Schick, Leonard H
  - Schlesinger, Arthur M
  - Schiller, A Arthur
  - Schmitt, Bernadotte E
  - Schnapper, M B
  - Schramm, Jacob R
  - Schutz(?), Albert
  - Schuyler, Robert Livingston
  - Schuylkill Book Service.
  - Science Service
  - Scientific American.
  - Scott, Ernest
  - Scott, Franklin D
  - Scott, Hugh
  - Scribner, Charles, and Sons
  - Scull, E Marshall
  - Second Presbyterian Church of Philadelphia.
  - Segal, Bernard G
  - Seifriz, William
  - Seitz, Richard M
  - Sellers, Charles Coleman, 1903-
  - Sellery, G C
  - Sellin, J Thorsten
  - Selsam, J Paul
  - Senior Banquet--Speech after dinner, 1908
  - Serbian Relief Committee of America.
  - Setton, Kenneth M
  - Shackleton, Emily
  - Shafer, Joseph
  - Sharp, Alex
  - Sharp, F C
  - Shea, William G
  - Shearer, Augustus H
  - Sheehan, M E
  - Shephard, Willard C
  - Sherriff, Florence Janson
  - Shipley, F W
  - Shoemaker, Alice
  - Shoener, Elizabeth S
  - Shotwell, James T
  - Shryock, Richard Harrison, 1893-1972.
  - Shuckle(?), John
  - Sibley, Elbert
  - Siegel, C
  - Simpson, Hartley
  - Simpson, J
  - Siousatt, Mrs. Julia T
  - Sioussat, St. George
  - Skilling, H Gordon
  - Smith, Alec H
  - Smith, Charles E
  - Smith, Edgar Fahs
  - Smith, Mrs. Estell Sergeant
  - Smith, J Russell
  - Smith, J Somers, Jr.
  - Smith, Marion Parris
  - Smith, Phillip V S
  - Smith, Rhea Marsh
  - Snyderman, G
  - Society of American Historians.
  - Society of Colonial Wars
  - Solis-Cohen, Solomon
  - Somerville, J Ernest
  - Sontag, Raymond J
  - Soule, Phelps
  - Spaeth, J Duncan
  - Spangler, Earl
  - Spiller, Robert E
  - Squair, J
  - Stahl, Margaret Macfeat
  - Stamp, A E
  - Stang, Fredrik
  - Starr, Mrs. Louis
  - Steefel, Lawrence D
  - Stefansson, Vilhjalmur, 1879-1962
  - Stein, Karl Eugene
  - Steinberg, R Philip
  - Stevens, David H
  - Stevens, Lewis M
  - Stevens, S K
  - Stevens, William M
  - Stevenson, Christine Wetherell
  - Stevenson, John A
  - Stiefel, Israel
  - Stimson, Henry L
  - Stine, Harold S
  - Stoddard, A J
  - Stokes, J Stogdell
  - Stokes, Joseph, Jr.
  - Stone, J L
  - Stone, Mark K
  - Store, Sarah Logan
  - Story of Philosophical Hall
  - Stoudt, John Joseph
  - Strachey, J S
  - Stratton, Morton B
  - Strawbridge, Francis R
  - Strohecker, H F
  - Strong, James Fry
  - Sturtevant, Edgar H
  - Sudermann, G
  - Suhrie, Ambrose L
  - Summer School
  - Sunday School Lectures, Talks, Etc.
  - Swain, J E
  - Swain, J W
  - Swartz, George M
  - Sweeney, S B
  - Sweet, William W
  - Swindell, Fred H
  - Swinney, John B
  - Switzerland.
  - Tait, T F
  - Tasting, Mrs. M H
  - Taylor, Francis Henry
  - Taylor, George E
  - Taylor, Lily Ross
  - Taylor, Mrs. Paul F
  - Taylor, Peter K
  - Teachers' Institute Library.
  - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association
  - Tead, Mrs. Clara
  - Tempalle, Harold W
  - Temple University
  - Terminal Market for Philadelphia.
  - Terra, Helmut de
  - Terry, Arthur Guy
  - Thayer, John B
  - Thayer, Robert F
  - Thomas, Daniel H
  - Thompson, C Seymour
  - Thompson, H Keith
  - Thompson, James Westfall
  - Thornington, J Monroe
  - Timanus, J H R
  - Timken Roller Bearing Company.
  - Tolstoy, Ilya
  - Tower, Walter S
  - Traylor, M A
  - Trueholme, Norman M
  - Tucker, Chester E
  - Turner, Edward Raymond
  - Turner, Frederick J
  - Turner, Justin G
  - Twitmyer, Edward M
  - Union League of Philadelphia.
  - Union University.
  - United Presbyterian Church in the United States of America.
  - United States Citizens.
  - U. S. Department of State
  - U.S. National Archives.
  - U.S. Naval Academy.
  - United States Navy
  - U.S. President
  - U.S. President's Commission on Economy and Efficiency.
  - U. S. War Department
  - Universities and Progress
  - University of California - Riverside.
  - University of Chicago
  - University of Delaware.
  - University of Maryland.
  - University of Nebraska.
  - University of Nevada.
  - University of Pennsylvania
  - University of Pennsylvania. University Publication Committee
  - University of Toronto
  - University of Wyoming.
  - Unknown
  - Valentin, Veit
  - Van Alen, William L
  - VanBibber, Lena C
  - Vanderbilt, Paul
  - Van Doren, Carl
  - Van Eysinga, J H
  - Van Hamel, Joseph A
  - Van Nostrand, J J, Jr.
  - Van Tyne, C H
  - Van Tyne, Isobel
  - Vaughan, Samuel
  - Vaughn, E V
  - Vaurs, Roger
  - Vollbrecht, W F
  - Volwiler, A T
  - Von Wegerer, Alfred
  - Wagner Lutheran College., Honorary Degree
  - Waldo, Fullerton L
  - Walker, Curtis H
  - Wallace, Paul A W
  - Wallace, Willard M
  - Wallace, Wiliametta
  - Wallach, Hans
  - Walnut Street Presbyterian Church.
  - War Price Rationing Board.
  - Wartime Prohibition Association of Philadelphia.
  - Warner, William H G
  - Washington, Patty W
  - Watney, Charles
  - Watney, Frank D
  - Watson, Frank D
  - Watson, John
  - Watts, Elizabeth
  - Wayland, Francis F
  - Weaver, George
  - Weaver, Warren
  - Webster, Charles H
  - Wendel, Hugo C M
  - Wenrich, David H
  - West Philadelphia Corporation.
  - Westergaard, Waldemar
    Westergaard, Waldemar, 1882-1963
  - Westermann
  - Wetherill, Samuel P
  - Weygandt, Cornelius N
  - Wharton, Anne H
  - Wharton Review.
  - Whitaker, Arthur P
  - Whitbeck, R H
  - Whitcomb, Merrick
  - White, Dimitri Fedotoff
  - White, Dorothy Shipley
  - White, J William
  - White, Paul L., 1896-
  - White, Thomas Raeburn
  - White, Mrs. Thomas Raeburn
  - Whitehead, James L
  - Whitehill, Walter Muir
  - Whitehouse, J Howard
  - Whitney, Henry M
  - Who's who in America
  - Wickersham, J Harold
  - William and Mary Quarterly.
  - Williams, Alfred H
  - Williams, Mary Floyd
  - Wilson, L L W
  - Wilson, Woodrow, Pres.U.S., 1856-1924
  - Wintle, Lambert F
  - Wistar, Thomas, Jr.
  - Wistar Association
  - Wistar Party.
  - Witte, Hans
  - Wittefogel, Karl A
  - Wolf, Edwin, II
  - Wolff, Hellmüth
  - Wolgast
  - Womans Club of Salem, New Jersey.
  - Wood, Dean Earl
  - Wood, Horatic C, Jr.
  - Woodburn, James A
  - Woods, Arthur, 1870-1942
  - Woods, Charles
  - Workman, F Bullock
  - Workman, W Hunter
  - Wortman, J E
  - Wrench, Evelyn
  - Wright, Frank
  - Wright, Louis B
  - Wrong, George M
  - Wurts, John S
  - Yakobson, Sergei
  - Yale University
  - Yates, Jailey
  - Yegerlehner, John
  - Yeomans, Earl R
  - Young, James K
  - Young, Mrs. Louisa A
  - Young, Mabel Chant
  - Young, Ward H
  - Yugoslovia.
  - Zahn, Mabel A
  - Zimmern, Alfred
  - Zirkle, Conway
  - Zook, Mrs. Nancy
- Photographs, 16.0 Photograph(s); This list represents a sample of the available photographs in the William Lingelbach papers.
  - William Ezra Lingelbach wearing graduation cap and robe, 1.0 Photograph(s); Formal portrait of Lingelbach at a young age, wearing graduation attire.
  - William Ezra Lingelbach, sitting in automobile with two small children, informal portrait, 1907 September; 1.0 Photograph(s); View of Lingelbach and two children in automobile, with top back, parked in front of a building.
  - William Ezra Lingelbach (?), bust, sitting, formal portrait, n. d.; 1.0 Photograph(s); 3/4 formal portrait.
  - William Ezra Lingelbach, 3/4 length, sitting, portrait, ca. 1895; 1.0 Photograph(s); Half length view of Lingelbach seated in wooded chair.
  - 3/4 view portrait of William Ezra Lingelbach, n. d.; 1.0 Photograph(s); Formal portrait of Lingelbach.
  - William Ezra Lingelbach, formal portrait, n. d.; 1.0 Photograph(s); Bust length formal portrait of Lingelbach.
  - William Ezra Lingelbach, profile, 3/4 length, informal, standing in front of radio microphone, 1.0 Photograph(s); Profile view of Lingelbach standing in front of WCAU radio microphone, holding a sheet of paper.
  - William Ezra Lingelbach, in cap and gown, 3/4 length, with unidentified man also wearing cap and gown, 1.0 Photograph(s); Lingelbach standing with unidentified man, plants and window in background.
  - William Ezra Lingelbach at beach, n. d.; 1.0 Photograph(s); Half length view of Lingelbach, lying on this side on the beach.
  - William Ezra Lingelbach (?) and family, seated outside, group portrait, ca. 1960; 1.0 Photograph(s); Group portrait of family sitting outside, trees and water in background.
  - William Ezra Lingelbach, seated at desk, reading book, ca. 1960; 1.0 Photograph(s); Half length view of Lingelbach, seated at desk, holding open book, bookshelves and bust of Benjamin Franklin in background.
  - William Ezra Lingelbach, seated in chair, holding book, ca. 1960; 1.0 Photograph(s); Full length view of Lingelbach, seated in chair, photographs on table in background.
  - William Ezra Lingelbach, seated, holding open book, n. d.; 1.0 Photograph(s); Full length view of Lingelbach, sitting in chair, legs crossed, holding book, table with lamp and bookshelves in background.
  - William Ezra Lingelbach, standing, half length, with three unidentified men looking at a Benjamin Franklin manuscript, informal, 1.0 Photograph(s); Group portrait of four men, holding manuscript, bookshelves in background.
  - William Ezra Lingelbach seated outside, wearing hat, ca. 1960; 1.0 Photograph(s); Full length view of Lingelbach sitting on low wall outside, wearing hat, plants and house in background.
  - William Ezra Lingelbach, bust,sitting, portrait, ca. 1960; 1.0 Photograph(s); Formal portrait, 3/4 view of Lingelbach.